Once you've downloaded Python, you will find it in your folder and it's simple to now install it,
all you've got to do is double click on the package file.
Whatever it is.
If you're using a windows is the zip file and then follow the instructions.
As you know, it's just pressing lots of continues agreeing you can change the location, etc. and you
may need to put in your password.
If you're on a mac when you're installing your software, do that and it will then install the software
for you.
Now it really is quite a simple and straightforward process.
It will do it all for you and there is not much to it.
There you go.
Python is ready to roll.